{
    "subject": "resource/Paessler",
    "predicate": "property/foundation",
    "object": "resource/Nuremberg,_Germany",
    "human_readable": "Paessler was founded in Nuremberg, Germany.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8813520073890686,
            "question": "Who founded Paessler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8748376965522766,
            "question": "Where was Paessler founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8342446088790894,
            "question": "When was Paessler founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7877875566482544,
            "question": "In what city was Paessler established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7321679592132568,
            "question": "Is Nuremberg located in Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5475304126739502,
            "question": "Does Paessler have any branches outside of Nuremberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4597635269165039,
            "question": "What country is Nuremberg in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31438812613487244,
            "question": "What industry is Paessler involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.305763840675354,
            "question": "Is Paessler a well-known company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15006327629089355,
            "question": "What are some products or services offered by Paessler?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paessler was founded in Nuremberg, Germany.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6158_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paessler a well-known company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6158_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industry is Paessler involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6158_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Nuremberg in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6158_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6158_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Paessler AG was founded in 1997 and based in Nuremberg, Germany."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Paessler AG was founded in the metropolitan region of Nuremberg, Bayern, Germany. This supports the statement that Paessler was founded in Nuremberg, Germany."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}